Department of Geography fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Course outlines and exams, 1965 - 1987; F-12-6; 1.55 m of textual records
  - Geography 342-, 1968 - 1977; F-12-6-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 12-16)
  - Geography 343-, 1968 - 1978; F-12-6-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 12-16)
  - Geography 344-, 1968 - 1971; F-12-6-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 12-16)
  - Geography 344-, 1972 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 12-17)
  - Geography 345-, 1970 - 1978; F-12-6-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 12-17)
  - Geography 346-, 1978 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-84 (Archival box - standard 12-17)
  - Geography 349-, 1973 - 1975; F-12-6-0-0-85 (Archival box - standard 12-17)
  - Geography 351-, 1969 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-86 (Archival box - standard 12-17)
  - Geography 361-, 1975 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-87 (Archival box - standard 12-17)
  - Geography 362-, 1976 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-88 (Archival box - standard 12-17)
  - Geography 369-, 1975 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-89 (Archival box - standard 12-17)
  - Geography 375-, 1976 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-90 (Archival box - standard 12-17)
  - Geography 381-, 1967 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-91 (Archival box - standard 12-17)
  - Geography 382-, 1969 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-92 (Archival box - standard 12-17)
  - Geography 385-, 1979; F-12-6-0-0-93 (Archival box - standard 12-17)
  - Geography 403-, 1967 - 1968; F-12-6-0-0-94 (Archival box - standard 12-17)
  - Geography 404-, 1971 - 1973; F-12-6-0-0-95 (Archival box - standard 12-17)
  - Geography 405-, 1969 - 1977; F-12-6-0-0-96 (Archival box - standard 12-17)
  - Geography 406-, 1968 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-97 (Archival box - standard 12-17)
  - Geography 407-, 1968 - 1974; F-12-6-0-0-98 (Archival box - standard 12-18)
  - Geography 407-, 1975 - 1976; F-12-6-0-0-99 (Archival box - standard 12-18)
  - Geography 407-, 1977 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-100 (Archival box - standard 12-18)
  - Geography 413-, 1970 - 1971; F-12-6-0-0-101 (Archival box - standard 12-18)
  - Geography 413-, 1972; F-12-6-0-0-102 (Archival box - standard 12-18)
  - Geography 413-, 1973 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-103 (Archival box - standard 12-18)
  - Geography 414-, 1967 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-104 (Archival box - standard 12-18)
  - Geography 415-, 1967 - 1971; F-12-6-0-0-105 (Archival box - standard 12-18)
  - Geography 415-, 1972 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-106 (Archival box - standard 12-18)
  - Geography 416-, 1970 - 1978; F-12-6-0-0-107 (Archival box - standard 12-18)
  - Geography 418-, 1978; F-12-6-0-0-108 (Archival box - standard 12-18)
  - Geography 419-, 1976 - 1978; F-12-6-0-0-109 (Archival box - standard 12-18)
  - Geography 420-, 1971 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-110 (Archival box - standard 12-19)
  - Geography 421-, 1967 - 1972; F-12-6-0-0-111 (Archival box - standard 12-19)
  - Geography 421-, 1973 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-112 (Archival box - standard 12-19)
  - Geography 422-, 1971 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-113 (Archival box - standard 12-19)
  - Geography 424-, 1970 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-114 (Archival box - standard 12-19)
  - Geography 425-, 1969 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-115 (Archival box - standard 12-19)
  - Geography 429-, 1977 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-116 (Archival box - standard 12-19)
  - Geography 431-, 1973 - 1976; F-12-6-0-0-117 (Archival box - standard 12-19)
  - Geography 441-, 1968 - 1971; F-12-6-0-0-118 (Archival box - standard 12-19)
  - Geography 441-, 1972 - 1977; F-12-6-0-0-119 (Archival box - standard 12-19)
  - Geography 442-, 1967 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-120 (Archival box - standard 12-19)
  - Geography 443-, 1968 - 1973; F-12-6-0-0-121 (Archival box - standard 12-19)
  - Geography 444-, 1978 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-122 (Archival box - standard 12-20)
  - Geography 445-, 1979; F-12-6-0-0-123 (Archival box - standard 12-20)
  - Geography 449-, 1977 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-124 (Archival box - standard 12-20)
  - Geography 452-, 1971 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-125 (Archival box - standard 12-20)
  - Geography 461-, 1967 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-126 (Archival box - standard 12-20)
  - Geography 462-, 1967 - 1975; F-12-6-0-0-127 (Archival box - standard 12-20)
  - Geography 462-, 1976 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-128 (Archival box - standard 12-20)
  - Geography 463-, 1969 - 1973; F-12-6-0-0-129 (Archival box - standard 12-20)
  - Geography 464-, 1973 - 1978; F-12-6-0-0-130 (Archival box - standard 12-20)
  - Geography 465-, 1973; F-12-6-0-0-131 (Archival box - standard 12-20)
  - Geography 466-, 1972 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-132 (Archival box - standard 12-20)
  - Geography 467-, 1967 - 1978; F-12-6-0-0-133 (Archival box - standard 12-20)
  - Geography 468-, 1972; F-12-6-0-0-134 (Archival box - standard 12-20)
  - Geography 469-, 1968 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-135 (Archival box - standard 12-20)
  - Geography 470-, 1978; F-12-6-0-0-136 (Archival box - standard 12-20)
  - Geography 475-, 1975 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-137 (Archival box - standard 12-21)
  - Geography 491-, 1967 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-138 (Archival box - standard 12-21)
  - Geography 498-, 1974 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-139 (Archival box - standard 12-21)
  - Course proposals, 1969 - 1974; F-12-6-0-0-140 (Archival box - standard 12-21)
  - Anti-calendar, 1973; F-12-6-0-0-141 (Archival box - standard 12-21)
  - Anti-calendar, 1974; F-12-6-0-0-142 (Archival box - standard 12-21)
  - Anti-calendar, 1975; F-12-6-0-0-143 (Archival box - standard 12-21)
  - Anti-calendar, 1976; F-12-6-0-0-144 (Archival box - standard 12-21)
  - Anti-calendar - spring, 1977; F-12-6-0-0-145 (Archival box - standard 12-21)
  - Anti-calendar - summer, 1977; F-12-6-0-0-146 (Archival box - standard 12-21)
  - Anti-calendar - fall, 1977; F-12-6-0-0-147 (Archival box - standard 12-21)
  - Anti-calendar - spring, 1978; F-12-6-0-0-148 (Archival box - standard 12-22)
  - Anti-calendar - summer, 1978; F-12-6-0-0-149 (Archival box - standard 12-22)
  - Anti-calendar - fall, 1978; F-12-6-0-0-150 (Archival box - standard 12-22)
  - Course evaluations, 1979; F-12-6-0-0-151 (Archival box - standard 12-22)
  - Geography 221, 1972 - 1973; F-12-6-0-0-152 (Archival box - standard 12-13)
  - Geography Continuing Education Documentary Film Course, Prof. Eliot-Hurst, Geo/CE, Sunday Institute, 1974 - 1975; F-12-6-0-0-152.1 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 212 Natural Hazards; Summer, 1978; F-12-6-0-0-153 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 431 Landscape in Science, Art, Music; Spring, 1979; F-12-6-0-0-154 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 001 Geography of Technocratic Society; Spring, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-155 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 111 Physical Geography; Spring, Summer, Fall, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-156 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 112 Introductory Geology; Spring, Fall, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-157 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 121 Economic Geography; Spring, Summer Session, Fall (regular and EV), 1980; F-12-6-0-0-158 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 141 Social Geography; Spring (regular and EV), Summer, Fall, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-159 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 201 Geographical Ideas; Summer '80 and '82, 1980 - 1982; F-12-6-0-0-160 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 222 Special Issues in Economic Geography; Summer, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-161 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 242 Social Space; Spring, 1980; Fall 1984, Spring 1986, 1980 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-162 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 250 Cartography I; Spring, Summer (regular and EV), Fall, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-163 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 251 Methods in Spatial Analysis; Spring '80, '81 (regular and CS), Summer '80, Fall '80, 1980 - 1981; F-12-6-0-0-164 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 262 Canada; Spring, Summer, Fall, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-165 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 313 Geomorphology; Spring (regular and EV), Summer, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-166 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 314 Climatology; Spring, Fall, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-167 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 317 Soil Geography, Summer (and CS), Fall '80, Summer (CS), Fall (CS) '81, 1980 - 1981; F-12-6-0-0-168 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 318 Sedimentology and Past Environments; Spring (regular and EV), Fall (EV), 1980 - 1981; F-12-6-0-0-169 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 322 Geography of Primary Activities; Spring (regular and EV), Summer, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-170 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 323 Geography of Manufacturing; Spring (EV), Fall, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-171 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 324 Geography of Transportation; Spring (regular and CS), Fall, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-172 (Archival box - standard 12-23)
  - GEOG 325 Geography of Tertiary Activities; Fall' 80, Summer (EV) '81, 1980 - 1981; F-12-6-0-0-173 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 343 Geography of Transitional Societies; Fall (EV) '80, Spring, Summer, Fall '81, Fall '82, 1980 - 1982; F-12-6-0-0-174 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 344 Geography of Modern Industrial Societies; Spring (regular and CS), Fall, 1980 - 1981; F-12-6-0-0-175 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 346 Geography of Contemporary Industrial Society; Spring, (regular and DT EV), Summer, Fall (EV), 1980; F-12-6-0-0-176 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 351 Cartography II; Spring, Fall, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-177 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 361 Introduction to Urban Geography; Spring, Fall, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-178 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 362 Geography of Urban Development; Spring, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-179 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 369 Human Microgeography; Spring (EV), Fall, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-180 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 375 Historical Geography I; Fall, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-181 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 381 Political Geography; Summer '80, Fall '81, 1980 - 1981; F-12-6-0-0-182 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 382 Population Geography; Fall, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-183 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 383 Regional Planning I; Fall, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-184 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 385-3 Introduction to Agricultural Geography; Spring '80 and '81, 1980 - 1981; F-12-6-0-0-185 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 406 Geographical Methodology; Fall '80, Spring, Summer '81, Fall '82, 1980 - 1982; F-12-6-0-0-186 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 407 Quantitative Methods in Geography; Spring '80 and '81, Fall '83 and '87, 1980 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-187 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 413 Geomorphology II; Fall, 1980 - 1981; F-12-6-0-0-188 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 416 Pleistocene Geography; Spring and Fall, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-189 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 418 Terrain Evaluation; Spring '80, Spring and Fall (EV) '82, Spring '84, Summer '86, 1980 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-190 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 420 Comparative Cultural Geography; Spring, 1980 - 1981; F-12-6-0-0-191 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 421 Geography of Resources Development; Summer '80 and '81, Fall '81, 1980 - 1981; F-12-6-0-0-192 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 422 Geography of Lesser Developed Countries; Fall '80, Fall '87, 1980 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-193 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 424 Urban Transportation; Fall '80 '82-'86, 1980 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-194 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 425 Geography of Communications; Fall (EV DT) '80, Spring '83, 1980 - 1983; F-12-6-0-0-195 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 431 Landscape in Science, Art, Music and Literature; Spring '80 and '81, Spring and Summer '82, 1980 - 1982; F-12-6-0-0-196 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 441 Geography of Urban Regions; Summer '80 and '81, Spring '82-'87, 1980 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-197 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 444 Regional Planning II; Spring '80-'84, 1980 - 1983; F-12-6-0-0-198 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 445 Rural Planning; Fall '80, Spring '81, Fall '81-'83, Spring '84-'87, 1980 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-199 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 449 Selected Topics in Cultural Geography; Summer (EV/IS) '80, Summer '81, Fall '80 and '82-'84, '86-'87, 1980 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-200 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 452 Theoretical and Computer Cartography; Fall '80-'81. Spring, Fall '83. Spring, Fall '85, Summer '87, 1980 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-201 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 460 Selected Region: Soviet Union, Fall, 1980; F-12-6-0-0-202 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 462 Canada; Summer, Fall (Kelowna), 1980; F-12-6-0-0-203 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 464 Geography of Africa (South Sahara); Spring '80, '84, '86, Fall '81 and '82, 1980 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-204 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 469 Canadian North and Middle North; Fall '80-'81, Summer '84-'85, Spring '86-'87, 1980 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-205 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 470 Geography of Western Canada; Spring, Summer (EV/IS), Fall '80, Spring '82, 1980 - 1982; F-12-6-0-0-206 (Archival box - standard 12-24)
  - GEOG 101 General Geography; Fall '81, Spring '83, 1980 - 1983; F-12-6-0-0-207 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 111 Physical Geography; Spring, Fall, 1981; F-12-6-0-0-208 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 111 Physical Geography; Summer (regular and EV), 1981; F-12-6-0-0-209 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 112 Introductory Geology; Spring, Fall, 1981; F-12-6-0-0-210 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 121 Economic Geography; Spring, Fall (regular and EV), 1981; F-12-6-0-0-211 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 141 Social Geography; Spring (regular and EV), Summer, Fall, 1981; F-12-6-0-0-212 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 212 Geography of Natural Hazards; Fall '81 and Spring '82, 1981 - 1982; F-12-6-0-0-213 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 250 Cartography; Spring, Fall (regular and EV), 1981; F-12-6-0-0-214 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 262 Canada; Spring (regular and EV), Summer, Fall, 1981; F-12-6-0-0-215 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 263 Selected Regions; Spring (regular and EV), 1981; F-12-6-0-0-216 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 313 Geomorphology; Spring (EV), Summer (IS), 1981; F-12-6-0-0-217 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 314 Climatology; Fall, 1981; F-12-6-0-0-218 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 315 Biogeography; Fall, 1981; F-12-6-0-0-219 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 322 Geography of Primary Activities; Spring, Fall (EV), 1981; F-12-6-0-0-220 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 324 Geography of Transportation; Spring, Fall, 1981; F-12-6-0-0-221 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 351 Cartography II; Spring, Fall, 1981; F-12-6-0-0-222 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 361 Introduction to Urban Geography; Spring, Fall, 1981; F-12-6-0-0-223 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 375-3 Historical Geography I; Spring (regular and EV DT); Spring and Summer (EV) '82, 1981 - 1982; F-12-6-0-0-224 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 383 Regional Planning; Spring, Summer, Fall, 1981; F-12-6-0-0-225 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 414 Climatology II; Spring '81 and Spring (EV) '82; Spring '83, 1981 - 1983; F-12-6-0-0-226 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 415 Biogeography II; Spring '81, '82, '83, 1981 - 1983; F-12-6-0-0-227 (Archival box - standard 12-25)
  - GEOG 416 Pleistocene Geography; Fall '81, Spring and Fall '82, Fall '83, 1981 - 1983; F-12-6-0-0-228 (Archival box - standard 12-26)
  - GEOG 429 Selected Topics in Economic Geography; Spring (regular and EV), Summer '81-'82, (EV) '84, Fall '86, 1981 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-229 (Archival box - standard 12-26)
  - GEOG 460 Selected Regions of British Columbia; Spring '81; Spring (regular and Kelowna) '82, 1981 - 1982; F-12-6-0-0-230 (Archival box - standard 12-26)
  - GEOG 461 Western Europe; Spring, 1981; F-12-6-0-0-231 (Archival box - standard 12-26)
  - GEOG 462 Canada; Spring and Summer (EV), 1981; F-12-6-0-0-232 (Archival box - standard 12-26)
  - GEOG 475 Advanced Historical Geography II; Spring '81; Spring and Fall '82, Fall '87, 1981 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-233 (Archival box - standard 12-26)
  - GEOG 491 Geography Honors degree, 1981; F-12-6-0-0-234 (Archival box - standard 12-26)
  - GEOG 498 Field Studies in Geography; Fall '81-'84, 1981 - 1984; F-12-6-0-0-235 (Archival box - standard 12-26)
  - GEOG 111 Physical Geography; Spring, Summer (EV), 1982; F-12-6-0-0-236 (Archival box - standard 12-26)
  - GEOG 111 Physical Geography; Summer, Fall, 1982; F-12-6-0-0-237 (Archival box - standard 12-26)
  - GEOG 112 Introductory Geology; Spring, Summer (IS and regular), Fall, 1982; F-12-6-0-0-238 (Archival box - standard 12-26)
  - GEOG 121 Economic Geography; Spring, Summer, Fall (regular and EV DT), 1982; F-12-6-0-0-239 (Archival box - standard 12-26)
  - GEOG 141 Social Geography; Spring (regular and EV), Summer (regular and EV/SS), Fall (DT), 1982; F-12-6-0-0-240 (Archival box - standard 12-26)
  - GEOG 250 Cartography I; Spring, Summer (EV), Fall (regular and EV), 1982; F-12-6-0-0-241 (Archival box - standard 12-26)
  - GEOG 251 Methods in Spatial Analysis; Spring, Summer, 1982; F-12-6-0-0-242 (Archival box - standard 12-26)
  - GEOG 262 Canada; Spring, Fall (EV), 1982; F-12-6-0-0-243 (Archival box - standard 12-26)
  - GEOG 263 Selected Regions; Spring, Fall, 1982; F-12-6-0-0-244 (Archival box - standard 12-26)
  - GEOG 312 Geography of Natural Hazards; Fall, 1982; F-12-6-0-0-245 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 313 Geomorphology; Spring, Fall (EV), 1982; F-12-6-0-0-246 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 314 Climatology I; Spring, Fall, 1982; F-12-6-0-0-247 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 315 Biogeography I; Fall '82, Summer '83 (EV), Fall '84, 1982 - 1984; F-12-6-0-0-248 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 317 Soil Geography; Spring (EV) and Fall (CS) '82; Spring and Summer (CS) '83, Summer '84, 1982 - 1984; F-12-6-0-0-249 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 318 Sedimentology and Past Environments; Summer and Fall '82, '85-'86, Spring '84, 1982 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-250 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 322 Geography of Primary Activities; Spring '82, '83, '84, 1982 - 1984; F-12-6-0-0-251 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 323 Geography of Manufacturing; Fall '82, '83, '84, 1982 - 1984; F-12-6-0-0-252 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 324 Geography of Transportation; Spring (EV DT) '82, Fall '83, Summer (SS) '82 and (EV) '84, 1982 - 1984; F-12-6-0-0-253 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 325 Geography of Tertiary and Quaternary Activities; Spring '82 and '83, Fall '83 and '84 (EV), 1982 - 1984; F-12-6-0-0-254 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 344 Geography of Modern Industrial Societies; Fall, 1982; F-12-6-0-0-255 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 346 Geography of Contemporary Industrial Societies; Spring (EV DT and regular) and Summer '82, Spring '83, 1982 - 1983; F-12-6-0-0-256 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 351 Cartography II; Spring, Summer (EV/IS), Fall, 1982; F-12-6-0-0-257 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 353 Aerial Photographic Interpretation; Fall, 1982 - 1983; F-12-6-0-0-258 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 361 Introduction to Urban Geography; Fall '82, Spring (EV DT) and Fall '83, 1982 - 1983; F-12-6-0-0-259 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 369 Human Microgeography; Spring '82 and '83, Fall '83, 1982 - 1983; F-12-6-0-0-260 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 381 Political Geography; Fall '82 and '84, Spring '84, '86, '87, 1982 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-261 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 382 Population Geography; Spring '82, Spring and Fall '83, 1982 - 1983; F-12-6-0-0-262 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 383 Regional Planning I; Spring and Fall (EV and regular) '82, Spring and Fall '83, 1982 - 1983; F-12-6-0-0-263 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 385 Introduction to Agricultural Geography; Spring '82, Fall '83, F134 '85, 1982 - 1985; F-12-6-0-0-264 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 462 Geography of Canada; Summer, Fall, 1982; F-12-6-0-0-265 (Archival box - standard 12-27)
  - GEOG 111 Physical Geography; Spring, Summer (SS), Fall, 1983; F-12-6-0-0-266 (Archival box - standard 12-28)
  - GEOG 112 Introductory Geology; Spring (regular and EV), Fall, 1983 - 1984; F-12-6-0-0-267 (Archival box - standard 12-28)
  - GEOG 121 Economic Geography; Spring, Summer, Fall, 1983; F-12-6-0-0-268 (Archival box - standard 12-28)
  - GEOG 141 Social Geography; Spring, Fall (regular and EV), 1983; F-12-6-0-0-269 (Archival box - standard 12-28)
  - GEOG 250 Cartography I; Spring, Summer (EV), 1983; F-12-6-0-0-270 (Archival box - standard 12-28)
  - GEOG 250 Cartography I; Fall (regular and EV), 1983; F-12-6-0-0-271 (Archival box - standard 12-28)
  - GEOG 251 Methods in Spatial Analysis; Spring, Summer (CS)'83, Fall '83-'85, Spring, Fall '86-'87, 1983 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-272 (Archival box - standard 12-28)
  - GEOG 262 Canada; Summer, Fall (EV DT), 1983; F-12-6-0-0-273 (Archival box - standard 12-28)
  - GEOG 263 Selected Regions: BC; Latin America; Africa; Spring, 1983; F-12-6-0-0-274 (Archival box - standard 12-28)
  - GEOG 263 Western Europe; Summer '83; Spring '84, 1983 - 1984; F-12-6-0-0-275 (Archival box - standard 12-28)
  - GEOG 301 Geographic Ideas and Methodology; Spring, Summer, Fall, 1983; F-12-6-0-0-276 (Archival box - standard 12-28)
  - GEOG 311 Hydrology; Fall, 1983 - 1984; F-12-6-0-0-277 (Archival box - standard 12-28)
  - GEOG 312 Geography of Natural Hazards; Spring, Fall (regular and EV) '83, Fall '84, 1983 - 1984; F-12-6-0-0-278 (Archival box - standard 12-28)
  - GEOG 313 Geomorphology; Spring, Summer (SS), Fall '83 and '84, 1983 - 1984; F-12-6-0-0-279 (Archival box - standard 12-28)
  - GEOG 314 Climatology; Spring and Fall (regular and EV) '83; Spring and Fall '84, 1983 - 1984; F-12-6-0-0-280 (Archival box - standard 12-29)
  - GEOG 351 HydroCartology II; Spring and Fall (regular and EV) '83; Spring and Fall '84, 1983 - 1984; F-12-6-0-0-281 (Archival box - standard 12-29)
  - GEOG 362 Geography of Urban Development; Spring and Fall; Spring '87 and '87, 1983 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-282 (Archival box - standard 12-29)
  - GEOG 375 Historical Geography I; Spring, Fall (regular and EV) '83, Spring and Fall '84, 1983 - 1984; F-12-6-0-0-283 (Archival box - standard 12-29)
  - GEOG 413 Geomorphology I; Spring '83-'85 and '87, 1983 - 1987; F-12-6-0-0-284 (Archival box - standard 12-29)
  - GEOG 419 Remote Sensing; Spring [note: course number change to GEOG 453], 1983 - 1984; F-12-6-0-0-285 (Archival box - standard 12-29)
  - GEOG 420 Comparative Cultural Geography; Fall '83 and '84; Spring (EV DT) '84; Spring '86, 1983 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-286 (Archival box - standard 12-29)
  - GEOG 421 Geograpy of Resource Development; Spring, Summer, Fall '83; Spring '85; Fall '86, 1983 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-287 (Archival box - standard 12-29)
  - GEOG 462 Canada; Spring, Fall '83; Fall '85, 1983 - 1985; F-12-6-0-0-288 (Archival box - standard 12-29)
  - GEOG 470 Geography of Western Canada; Spring '83 and '84; Summer '86, 1983 - 1986; F-12-6-0-0-289 (Archival box - standard 12-29)
  - GEOG 101 General Geography; Spring (regular and DT) '84; Spring and Fall '85, 1984 - 1985; F-12-6-0-0-290 (Archival box - standard 12-29)
  - GEOG 111 Physical Geography; Spring (regular and EV), Summer (SS), Fall, 1984; F-12-6-0-0-291 (Archival box - standard 12-29)
  - GEOG 112 Introductory Geology; Spring, Fall, 1984; F-12-6-0-0-292 (Archival box - standard 12-29)
  - GEOG 121 Economic Geography; Spring (regular and EV, EV DT), Summer, Fall (regular and EV), 1984; F-12-6-0-0-293 (Archival box - standard 12-29)
  - GEOG 141 Social Geography; Spring, Summer, Fall (regular and DT), 1984 - 1985; F-12-6-0-0-294 (Archival box - standard 12-29)
  - GEOG 250 Cartography I; Spring, Summer, Fall, 1984; F-12-6-0-0-295 (Archival box - standard 12-29)
  - GEOG 262 Canada; Summer, Fall, 1984; F-12-6-0-0-296 (Archival box - standard 12-30)